We did add logic to load our ingredients
Maddelerimizi yklemek iin mantk ekledik.
and by the way, if you're wondering why the salad is at the bottom, that happens because since we loaded
Ve bu arada neden bir salata altta duruyor merak ediyorsanz,
from firebase and there we can't order the properties manually, the salad is ordered at the bottom alphabetically
nk biz ate bazndan yklediimizden oradan oraya elle sipari edemiyoruz salatalklar tbben dibinde
.
sipari ettik.
and therefore, it's at the bottom here
Ve bu nedenle burada alttadr.
too. You would simply have to adjust your code to manually turn your ingredients let's say into not just
iin bir nesne haline getiren maddeleri manuel olarak dndrmek iin ayarlamanz gerekir ve bu durumda bununla
a number as a value but an object where you also define the position and then you would have to adjust
ilgilenmek iin nnz ve kodunuzu ayarlamanz gerekir. pozisyonunuzu veya size tabii ki,
your frontend code to take care about this position too or you of course simply choose a solution where
malzemelerinizi sert kodladnz ve sunucudan aldnz ieriklere eit miktarda ierik koymadnz bir zm sein.
you hard code your ingredients and don't set ingredients equal to the ingredients you get back from
S Kodunuzu, yalnzca bir say olarak deil, ayn zamanda bir
the server
konum bulmak
but to a javascript object where you then manually map salad to action.ingredients.salad and so
Ancak elle haritalama yapmadnz bir javascript nesnesine eylem bileenleri satmak vb. Elbette ki elbette daha nce sahip
on, this of course then loses a bit of the flexibility you had before where you could simply take advantage
olduunuz esneklii biraz kaybederek neredeyse bir ey ayarlamann avantajndan yararlanabilir ve daha sonra bunu
of setting up anything and then using it in your frontend app, though you never had all that flexibility
kullanabilir n u uygulamanz olsa da, tm bu esneklii zaten hi kullanmadnz nk
anyways because we have only a limited amount of ingredients supported with our css code here and
bizimle snrl miktarda madde destekliyoruz. c. s s kodu burada ve
the ingredients property where we also have a switch case statement.
hepimiz bir switch case deyimi var maddeler zellii.
So just to complete that thought here, we can reach out to action.ingredients.cheese and so on here to map
balayn ve sipari tekrar doru olduundan imdi biz bunu manuel olarak haritalandryoruz.
this one by one when we set the ingredients, also with the meat of course and with all that added, you
te bu dnceyi burada tamamlamak iin biz aslnda Regans peynirimize ulaabiliriz ...
would see that now if we save this and go back to the application and start adding salad and so on, the
ve burada da eti tabayla koyduumuzda birer tane haritalamamz gerekiyor. bu
order is correct again because now, we're mapping this manually.
ve uygulamaya geri dnn ve salata eklemeye
Again the downside is since we have to do this, we really only support these four ingredients but we're
Yine dezavantaj, bunu yapmak zorundayz nk bu drt maddeyi yalnzca gerekten destekliyoruz ancak
doing this anyway in our application
bunu uygulamamzda zaten yapyoruz.
as I just said, for example in the ingredients component, in the burger area here where we also have a
rnein sadece burger Alannda bulunan maddeler bileeninde sylediim gibi, tmnde yalnzca snrl
switch case statement where we also only support a limited amount of components.
miktarda bileenleri destekleyen bir switch case deyimi var.
So this is the case anyways and now at least, the ordering is back to where it was before.
Bu durumda zaten byle ve en azndan emir nceki haline dnyor.
So this is one possible improvement, purely optional
Dolaysyla, bu olas bir iyiletirme tamamen istee baldr.
just wanted to make sure you are not confused why the salad is at the bottom.
Sadece neden Senatonun en altndayken kafanz karmadndan emin olmak istedim.